StefanoMunarini

Software Developer

contact

Jämeräntaival 6 B 207 Otaniemi, Espoo, 02150 +358 (0) 46 9424916 stefano.munarini@me.com

Skype:

stefano.munarini

accounts

LinkedIn:

munarinistefano

GitHub:

munarinistefano

StackOverflow:

2741833

languages

Italian mother tongue English proficient

programming

Python, Java, SQL, HTML, Javascript

certifications

IELTS Bandscore 7

about me

A passionate and well-rounded developer, with an high capacity of problem solving, who is able to convert complex problems into smaller and easier tasks. A good team player but also a team leader if needed, who is able to listen and to compare ideas with others to drive teams to better solutions.

A good background in web development with Python, Django, JavaScript, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Docker, Cron and Git achieved during his work experience in London, starting as an intern in a startup called TutorCruncher and continued as Python Developer at Tangent Snowball, a digital agency responsible for developing projects for clients such as PepsiCo, Sky, Carlsberg, Wolseley and many more.

A good background in Android development confirmed by the popularity (over 90k downloads) and the rating (4.5/5) of his application "Libretto Universitario" in the Google Play Store, and certified by the winning of the first price as "Best mobile application of 2013" at the UpperApp festival. A good academic background in web development with Java technologies, as well as with the Spring framework.

A natural explorer and a traveler who had met lots of different cultures that enabled him to open his mind while teaching him values such as respect, adaptability and integrity.

experience

Feb 2016 - Jul 2016

Python Developer

Tangent Snowball - London, UK

This role encompassed the development of CRM platforms for companies such as PepsiCo and Walkers. In particular, I was responsible for the development of a eCRM web platform for Wolseley and for the development and the maintenance of the Counts For More platform (PepsiCo).

The technology stack was made of Python (Django), JavaScript, HTML, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Docker, Git and Jira.

Jan 2016 - Feb 2016

Python Developer

TutorCruncher – London, UK

Responsible for developing, improving and extending functionalities of TutorCruncher, a cloud-based platform developed in Django.

Feb 2014 - Jun 2014

Android Developer

Dedagroup ICT Network - Trento, Italy

Responsible for designing and developing an Android application aimed at helping people affected by Alzheimer's Disease. The role encompassed all aspects of software design, both fronted and backend, including architectural decisions.

projects

Jul 2013 - Sep 2015

Libretto Universitario

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.povodev.libretto

Libretto Universitario is an Android application for Italian university students, which aims at helping and simplifying the management and the organization of one's university career. It is available for the download in the italian Google Play Store.

awards

Dec 2013

UpperApp Festival - 1st Prize: Best Mobile Application of 2013

Agorà Telematica

Libretto Universitario has been awarded as *Best Mobile Application* of 2013 at the UpperApp Festival.

education

2016 - 2017

EIT Digital Master School

Master Degree in Information Networks Aalto University, Finland (Entry University)

Major: Software and Service Architectures (SSA)

Minor: Innovation & Entrepreneurship (I&E)

2011 - 2015

Bachelor Degree in Computer Science

University of Trento, Italy